youworkforthem.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy - YouWorkForThem

Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to YouWorkForThem. By accessing and/or using YouWorkForThem.com, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. YouWorkForThem reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Your use of this site will be subject to the most current version of this Privacy Policy at the time of any such use. 

### Collection of personal information

When you access or use this site, YouWorkForThem may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, YouWorkForThem may ask that you provide us personal information, such as: your name, address, phone number, e-mail address and if you purchase products we will require your credit card and or PayPal details. If you do not fill out any forms, YouWorkForThem collects nothing about you other than your browser type, OS type and IP address. 

### How your personal information is used

YouWorkForThem collects your information strictly for billing and licensing. If you order a product that is to be electronically downloaded, for example, the information is used to verify credit cards, issue the appropriate license receipts and to maintain your customer history. 

### Protection of your personal information

The personal information that you provide is protected in several ways. Access by you to your personal information is available through a password and unique customer ID selected by you. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. In addition, your personal information resides on a secure server that only select YouWorkForThem personnel may access via password. YouWorkForThem protects your credit card transaction using SSL encryption and thereby prevents unauthorized parties from viewing such information when it is being transmitted to YouWorkForThem. We do not record or keep your full credit card information after your order has been placed. NO personal identities or any other account information is shared with any third parties, EVER. 

### Use of cookies

When you visit YouWorkForThem,com, you can use the site anonymously and access most information without revealing your identity. In order to enable our shopping cart, we use 'cookies' for automated administration purposes. A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your id card, helping to correlate your passwords, purchases, and preferences to your personal browser. It cannot be executed as code or deliver any type of viruses. 

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the option to decide whether or not to accept it. (For web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users who choose not to accept cookies will not be able to use all functions properly.) 

While YouWorkForThem uses cookies to ensure proper functioning of our shopping system, and our web server automatically logs the Internet IP address of your computer, this information does not identify you personally and you remain completely anonymous unless you have otherwise provided YouWorkForThem with personal information. 

### Updating your personal information

You have the right to access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences at any time. To edit your registration information, simply log into your Account Settings. 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us. 

Last updated on June 10, 2012
